Mehrdad Qasemkhani

DevOps Engineer



gasemkhani.mehrdad@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/gasemkhani-mehrdad



+989385200818



https://mehrdad-drpc.github.io/

Summary

Experienced DevOps Engineer high focus on CPaaS and UCaaS,

with a demonstrated history of working in the internet telephony industry.

Skilled in SQL and noSQL Databases, like Mysql, Postgres, Apache ChouchDB,

Functional and Object-Oriented Programming, like Erlang, Java and Python.

Linux and ShellScripting. DevOps tools, like Git, CI/CD, Docker, Ansible.

VoIP tools, like Kamailio, Asterisk, Freeswitch.

Some TCP/IP protocol like HTTP, HTTPS, SIP, RTP, SDP, NAT, IP, TCP, UDP.

Strong engineering professional graduated from Shamsipour and Raja university.

Experience



DevOps Engineer

Respina Networks & Beyond

Feb 2020 - Present (8 months +)

- Cloud Telecommunication Technology CPaaS, UCaaS
- Session Initiation Protocol
- Kamailio SIP-Server
- Asterisk/Freeswitch Softswitch
- Maintainer of own SIP-Trunk
- Maintainer of own HostedPBX
- Docker/ Docker-Compose
- Load Balancing and High Availability
- VRRP
- CI/CD
- Ansible

Backend Developer

Respina Networks & Beyond

Jun 2019 - Feb 2020 (9 months)

- Develop ARI(Asterisk RESTful Interface) with python and Django
- Develop Asterisk Call Manager Over The ARI



Python Developer

Kara Tadbir Hooshmand Kish

Jul 2017 - Jun 2018 (1 year)

- Analyzed, designed and developed of a RESTful API with Python, Flask, gREST and Neo4j, PostgreSQL, Kong, ... to serve 2.5 million subscribers
- Experienced with pair-programming of project with junior/senior developers

● Wrote some python's unit-test and integration-test to develop CI/CD



AVA Communication Industries Co.

Sep 2016 - Jan 2017 (5 months)

- Develop Server-Side Socket via C
- Develop Client-Side Socket via Javascript/PHP

Education



Raja

Bachelor's degree 2011 - 2013



Shamsipour Technical and Vocational College

Associate's degree 2009 - 2011

Skills

Linux • Programming • Voice over IP (VoIP) • DevOps • Internet Protocol Suite (TCP/IP) • Load Balancing • High Availability • Cluster Management • Scripting • Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD)